Finding Aid for Black Mask, 1920-1951.
UCLA Library Special Collections
Black Mask,
1920-1951.
Joseph T. Shaw, editor
16 boxes (8 linear ft.)
Black Mask was a detective fiction pulp magazine.
University of California, Los Angeles. Library Special Collections. Los Angeles, California 90095-1575
Administrative Information
Restrictions on Access
COLLECTION STORED OFF-SITE AT SRLF: Open for research. Advance notice required for access. Contact the UCLA Library Special Collections Reference Desk for paging information.
UCLA Catalog Record ID
UCLA Catalog Record ID: 3786559
Scope and Content
Black Mask was a detective fiction magazine. The Library owns most of the issues from 1920 through 1951, but we do not have the complete run. Please check the container list for specific issues.
Black Mask Online Resources
Galactic Central's Black Mask checklist
Wikipedia's Black Mask entry
Indexing Terms
The following terms have been used to index the description of this collection in the library's online public access catalog.
Subjects
Black Mask
Container List
- 1920
  - April 1920: Issue 1 (Box 1, Volume 1)
    photocopy; no cover
  - May 1920: Issue 2 (Box 1, Volume 1)
    Cover by William Grotz
  - July 1920: Issue 4 (Box 1, Volume 1)
    no cover
  - August 1920: Issue 5 (Box 1, Volume 1)
  - October 1920: Issue 1 (Box 1, Volume 2)
    Cover by William Grotz; cover corner missing
  - December 1920: Issue 3 (Box 1, Volume 2)
- 1921
  - January 1921: Issue 4 (Box 1, Volume 2)
    Cover by Archie Gunn. Cover damage and missing some of the edge
  - March 1921: Issue 6 (Box 1, Volume 2)
    Cover by unknown. Cover edges torn
  - April 1921: Issue 1 (Box 1, Volume 3)
    Cover by William Grotz. Cover torn and damage.
  - June 1921: Issue 3 (Box 1, Volume 3)
    No cover and photocopy
  - July 1921: Issue 4 (Box 1, Volume 3)
  - November 1921: Issue 2 (Box 1, Volume 4)
    Cover by unknown
  - December 1921: Issue 3 (Box 1, Volume 4)
    Cover by unknown.
- 1922
  - January 1922: Issue 4 (Box 1, Volume 4)
    Cover by unknown and very fragile.
  - February 1922: Issue 5 (Box 2, Volume 4)
    cover detach
  - May 1922: Issue 2 (Box 2, Volume 5)
    missing cover
  - June 1922: Issue 3 (Box 2, Volume 5)
  - October 1922: Issue 6 (Box 2, Volume 5)
    2 issues, one cover is faded.
  - September 1922: Issue 6 (Box 2, Volume 5)
  - November 1922: Issue 7 (Box 2, Volume 5)
    cover damage.
  - December 1922: Issue 8 (Box 2, Volume 5)
    cover detached
- 1923
  - January 1923: Issue 10 (Box 2, Volume 5)
  - February 1923: Issue 11 (Box 2, Volume 5)
    cover damage
  - March 1 1923: Issue 13 (Box 2, Volume 5)
    2 copies, 1 original and 1 photocopy
  - March 15 1923: Issue 14 (Box 2, Volume 5)
  - April 15 1923: Issue 2 (Box 2, Volume 6)
    April 15 1923; very fragile
  - May 15 1923: Issue 4 (Box 2, Volume 6)
  - June 1 1923: Issue 5 (Box 2, Volume 6)
  - July 1 1923: Issue 7 (Box 2, Volume 6)
  - July 1 1923: Issue 8 (Box 2, Volume 6)
  - July 15 1923: Issue 8 (Box 2, Volume 6)
  - August 15 1923: Issue 10 (Box 3, Volume 6)
  - September 1 1923: Issue 11 (Box 3, Volume 6)
  - November 1 1923: Issue 14 (Box 3, Volume 6)
    photocopy
  - October 15 1923: Issue 14 (Box 3, Volume 6)
  - November 1 1923: Issue 15 (Box 3, Volume 6)
  - November 15 1923: Issue 16 (Box 3, Volume 6)
  - December 1 1923: Issue 17 (Box 3, Volume 6)
  - December 15 1923: Issue 18 (Box 3, Volume 6)
- 1924
  - January 1 1924: Issue 19 (Box 3, Volume 6)
  - January 15 1924: Issue 20 (Box 3, Volume 6)
  - February 1 1924: Issue 21 (Box 3, Volume 6)
  - February 15 1924: Issue 22 (Box 3, Volume 6)
  - March 1 1924: Issue 23 (Box 3, Volume 6)
  - March 15 1924: Issue 24 (Box 3, Volume 6)
  - April 1 1924: Issue 1 (Box 3, Volume 7)
  - April 15 1924: Issue 2 (Box 3, Volume 7)
  - July 1924: Issue 5 (Box 4, Volume 7)
  - August 1924: Issue 6 (Box 4, Volume 7)
  - September 1924: Issue 7 (Box 4, Volume 7)
  - October 1924: Issue 8 (Box 4, Volume 7)
  - November 1924: Issue 9 (Box 4, Volume 7)
- 1925
  - February 1925: Issue 12 (Box 4, Volume 7)
    photocopy; black buckram cover and volume number is 8 on the spine.
  - August 1925: Issue 6 (Box 4, Volume 8)
  - October 1925: Issue 8 (Box 4, Volume 8)
- 1926
  - March 1926: Issue 1 (Box 4, Volume 9)
    cover torn
  - April 1926: Issue 2 (Box 4, Volume 9)
  - May 1926: Issue 3 (Box 4, Volume 9)
  - August 1926: Issue 6 (Box 4, Volume 9)
    cover fragile
  - September 1926: Issue 7 (Box 4, Volume 9)
    very fragile
  - November 1926: Issue 9 (Box 4, Volume 9)
  - December 1926: Issue 10 (Box 4, Volume 9)
    cover torn and fragile
- 1927
  - January 1927: Issue 11 (Box 4, Volume 9)
  - February 1927: Issue 12 (Box 5, Volume 9)
  - March 1927: Issue 1 (Box 5, Volume 10)
  - April 1927: Issue 2 (Box 5, Volume 10)
  - May 1927: Issue 3 (Box 5, Volume 10)
  - June 1927: Issue 4 (Box 5, Volume 10)
  - July 1927: Issue 5 (Box 5, Volume 10)
  - August 1927: Issue 6 (Box 5, Volume 10)
  - September 1927: Issue 7 (Box 5, Volume 10)
  - October 1927: Issue 8 (Box 5, Volume 10)
  - November 1927: Issue 9 (Box 5, Volume 10)
  - December 1927: Issue 10 (Box 5, Volume 10)
- 1928
  - January 1928: Issue 11 (Box 5, Volume 10)
  - February 1928: Issue 12 (Box 5, Volume 10)
  - March 1928: Issue 1 (Box 5, Volume 11)
  - April 1928: Issue 2 (Box 5, Volume 11)
  - May 1928: Issue 3 (Box 5, Volume 11)
  - June 1928: Issue 4 (Box 5, Volume 11)
  - July 1928: Issue 5 (Box 5, Volume 11)
  - August 1928: Issue 6 (Box 5, Volume 11)
  - September 1928: Issue 7 (Box 5, Volume 11)
  - October 1928: Issue 8 (Box 6, Volume 11)
    Cover by Fred Craft -- "Black Sheep's Return" by Nels LeRoy Jorgensen
  - November 1928: Issue 9 (Box 6, Volume 11)
    Cover by Fred Craft -- "Black Lives" by Dashiell Hammett and "The Sky Trap" by Raoul F Whitfield
  - December 1928: Issue 10 (Box 6, Volume 11)
    Cover by J.W. Schlaikjer -- "The Next Stiff: an Ed Jenkins Story" by Erle Stanley Gardner and "Over the River" by Eugene Cunningham
- 1929
  - January 1929: Issue 11 (Box 6, Volume 11)
    Photocopy; Cover by Fred Craft -- "One Crook to Another: an Ed Jenkins Story" by Erle Stanley Gardner and "Black Honeymoon" by Dashiell Hammett
  - February 1929: Issue 12 (Box 6, Volume 11)
    Photocopy;Cover by J.W. Schlaikjer -- "Laughing Death" by Raoul Whitfield and "The Taste of Blood" by Tom Curry
  - March 1929: Issue 1 (Box 6, Volume 12)
    Cover by Fred Craft --"Race Williams in tags of Death" by Carroll John Daly
  - April 1929: Issue 2 (Box 6, Volume 12)
    Cover by H. C. Murphy, Jr.-- "The Six-Gun Showdown" by Edward Parrish Ware
  - May 1929: Issue 3 (Box 6, Volume 12)
    Photocopy; Cover by Fred Craft -- "Graft" by Frederick L. Nebel
  - June 1929: Issue 4 (Box 6, Volume 12)
    Cover by Fred Craft -- "Race Williams Never Bluffs" by Carroll John Daly
  - July 1929: Issue 5 (Box 6, Volume 12)
    Cover by Henry C. Murphy, Jr. -- "Crossed Lead" by Oliver Swett and "All the Way" by Erle Stanley Gardner
  - August 1929: Issue 6 (Box 6, Volume 12)
    Cover by Fred Craft -- "Fly Paper" by Dashiell Hammett and "The Other Cameo" by Earl & Marion Scott. Dashiell Hammett's Fly Paper is missing.
  - September 1929: Issue 7 (Box 6, Volume 12)
    2 copies (photocopy) Cover by Henry C. Murphy Jr. -- "The Maltese Falcon" by Dashiell Hammett
  - October 1929: Issue 8 (Box 6, Volume 12)
    Photocopy, cover by J. W. Schlaikjer -- "Hell's Stepsons" by Horace McCoy
  - November 1929: Issue 9 (Box 6, Volume 12)
    Cover by J. W. Schlaikjer -- "Hell-Smoke" by Frederick Nebel
  - December 1929: Issue 10 (Box 6, Volume 12)
    Cover by J. W. Schlaikjer -- "The Crime Breeders" by Raoul Whitfield
- 1930
  - January 1930: Issue 11 (Box 6, Volume 12)
    Photocopy; cover by J. W. Schlaikjer -- "Tough Treatment for a Tough Town" by Frederick Nebel
  - February 1930: Issue 12 (Box 6, Volume 12)
    Cover by J. W. Schlaikjer -- "The Farewell Murder, a Complete Novelette" by Dashiell Hammett
  - March 1930: Issue 1 (Box 6, Volume 13)
    Very brittle; cover by J. W. Schlaikjer -- "The Glass Key" by Dashiell Hammett. Photocopy of "Death in the Pasig" by Ramon Decolta( aka. Raoul Whitfield)pages 49 - 56.
  - April 1930: Issue 2 (Box 6, Volume 13)
    Cover by J. W. Schlaikjer -- "Wise Guy" by Frederick Nebel and Murderers Night by J. J. des Ormeaux
  - May 1930: Issue 3 (Box 7, Volume 13)
    Cover by J. W. Schlaikjer -- "Street Wof" by Frederick Nebel and "The Crime Crusher" by Erle Stanley Gardner
  - June 1930: Issue 4 (Box 7, Volume 13)
    Cover by J. W. Schlaikjer -- "Tainted Power: A Story of Race Williams" by Carroll John Daly
  - July 1930: Issue 5 (Box 7, Volume 13)
    Cover by J. W. Schlaikjer -- "Somewhere in Mexico: A Complete Novelette" by Horace McCoy and "Strumming Sam Malone" by Cleve Myers
  - August 1930: Issue 6 (Box 7, Volume 13)
    Cover and first page are detached; Cover by J. W. Schlaikjer -- "Ten Men from Chicago" by Frederick Nebel, "Murder by Mistake" by Raoul Whitefield, and "The Gunrunner" by Horace McCoy
  - September 1930: Issue 7 (Box 7, Volume 13)
    Cover by J. W. Schlaikjer -- "Death in a Bowl" by Raoul Whitefield
  - October 1930: Issue 8 (Box 7, Volume 13)
    Cover by J. W. Schlaikjer -- "The Dark Pack" by Nels Leroy Jorgensen and "Shooting out of Turn" by Carroll John Daly
  - November 1930: Issue 9 (Box 7, Volume 13)
    Torn cover; Cover by J. W. Schlaikjer -- "Rough Justice" by Frederick Nebel and "Lone Hand Tactics" by Nels Leroy Jorgensen
  - December 1930: Issue 10 (Box 7, Volume 13)
    Photocopy; Cover by J. W. Schlaikjer -- "Murder in the Ring" by Raoul Whitefield and "The Red-Hots" by Frederick Nebel
- 1931
  - January 1931: Issue 11 (Box 7, Volume 13)
    very brittle; photocopy of pages 98-100; Cover by J. W. Schlaikjer -- "Gun Thunder" by Frederick Nebel, "Trailing Trouble" by Arthur H. Hood, "Hard to Kill" by E. and M. Scott, "Stolen Justice" by Tom Curry, and "Silence House" by Ramon Decolta
  - February 1931: Issue 12 (Box 7, Volume 13)
    Cover by J. W. Schlaikjer -- "Derelict" by Joseph T. Shaw
  - March 1931: Issue 1 (Box 7, Volume 14)
    Cover by J. W. Schlaikjer -- "Murder by Mail" By Carroll John Daly
  - April 1931: Issue 2 (Box 7, Volume 14)
    Cover by J. W. Schlaikjer -- "Breed of Steel" by Jack Bertin
  - June 1931: Issue 4 (Box 7, Volume 14)
    Cover by J. W. Schlaikjer -- "'The Flame' and Race Williams" by Carroll John Daly
  - July 1931: Issue 5 (Box 7, Volume 14)
    Cover detached; Cover by J. W. Schlaikjer -- "Tommy Talks" by Erle Stanley Gardner
  - August 1931: Issue 6 (Box 7, Volume 14)
    Cover by J. W. Schlaikjer -- "The Skyline Murders" by Raoul Whitefield, "Spare the Rod" by Frederick Nebel, and "Race Williams and 'The Flame'" by Carroll John Daly
  - September 1931: Issue 7 (Box 7, Volume 14)
    Cover by J. W. Schlaikjer -- "All Star Favorites Number"
  - October 1931: Issue 8 (Box 7, Volume 14)
    Cover by J. W. Schlaikjer -- "Every Move a Picture" by Thomson Burtis, "Death's Not Enough" by Frederick Nebel, "Steel Arena" by Raoul Whitefield, and "The Hot Squat" by Erle Stanley Gardner
  - November 1931: Issue 9 (Box 7, Volume 14)
    Cover by J. W. Schlaikjer -- "It's the Live Ones that Talk" by Frederick Nebel
  - December 1931: Issue 10 (Box 7, Volume 14)
    Cover by J. W. Schlaikjer -- "Strictly Personal" by Erle Stanley Gardner
- 1932
  - January 1932: Issue 11 (Box 7, Volume 14)
    Cover by J. W. Schlaikjer -- "The Devil's Protégé" by Jack Bertin, "Table Stakes" by Stewart Stirling, and "China Man" by Ramon Decolta
  - February 1932: Issue 12 (Box 7, Volume 14)
    very brittle; Cover by James McArdle -- "The Box in the Hold" by H. Bedford- Jones; photocopy of "Inside Job" by Raoul Whitefield pages 8-31
  - March 1932: Issue 1 (Box 7, Volume 15)
    Cover by J. W. Schlaikjer -- "Feet First" by Erle Stanley Gardner and "Fast One" by Paul Cain
  - April 1932: Issue 2 (Box 7, Volume 15)
    Cover by J. W. Schlaikjer -- "The Amateur Murderer" by Carroll John Daly
  - May 1932: Issue 3 (Box 8, Volume 15)
    Cover by J. W. Schlaikjer -- "Walking Dynamite" by Raoul Whitefield
  - June 1932: Issue 4 (Box 8, Volume 15)
    Cover by J. W. Schlaikjer -- "Velvet" by Paul Cain
  - July 1932: Issue 5 (Box 8, Volume 15)
    Cover by J. W. Schlaikjer -- "The Devil Suit" by J. J. des Ormeaux
  - August 1932: Issue 6 (Box 8, Volume 15)
    Cover by J. W. Schlaikjer -- "Shake-up" by Frederick Nebel
  - September 1932: Issue 7 (Box 8, Volume 15)
    Cover by J. W. Schlaikjer -- "Blue Murder" by Raoul Whitefield and "He Could Take It" by Frederick Nebel
  - October 1932: Issue 8 (Box 8, Volume 15)
    Cover by J. W. Schlaikjer -- "Wings Over Texas" by Horace McCoy and "Party from Detroit" by Theodore Tinsley
  - November 1932: Issue 9 (Box 8, Volume 15)
    Cover by J. W. Schlaikjer -- "Sinful Cibola" by Jack Bertin and "Dead Men Tell Tales" by Raoul Whitefield
  - December 1932: Issue 10 (Box 8, Volume 15)
    Cover by J. W. Schlaikjer -- "Red Pavement" by Frederick Nebel
- 1933
  - December 1933: Issue 10 (Box 2, Volume 16)
    Cover by J. W. Schlaikjer -- "Dead Men's Shoes" by Erle Stanley Gardner, and "Blackmailers Don't Shoot" by Raymond Chandler; Folder 36
  - January 1933: Issue 11 (Box 8, Volume 15)
    Cover by J. W. Schlaikjer -- "Close Call" by Erle Stanley Gardner, "Murder by Request" by Raoul Whitefield, and "The Deal" by John Onslow
  - February 1933: Issue 12 (Box 8, Volume 15)
    Cover by J. W. Schlaikjer -- "K. O. Comes Clear" by William Rollins, Jr. and "Doors in the Dark: A Story of Capt. Steve MacBride" by Frederick Nebel
  - March 1933: Issue 1 (Box 8, Volume 16)
    Cover by J. W. Schlaikjer -- "Red Jade" by Erle Stanley Gardner
  - April 1933: Issue 2 (Box 8, Volume 16)
    Cover by J. W. Schlaikjer -- "Give the Man Rope" by H. H. Stinson
  - May 1933: Issue 3 (Box 8, Volume 16)
    Cover by J. W. Schlaikjer -- "Tequila" by John Bertin and "The Death Drop" by Carroll John Daly
  - June 1933: Issue 4 (Box 8, Volume 16)
    Cover by J. W. Schlaikjer -- "Save Your Tears: A Story of 'Tough Dick' Donahue" by Frederick Nebel
  - July 1933: Issue 5 (Box 8, Volume 16)
    Cover by J. W. Schlaikjer -- "Song and Dance" by Frederick Nebel
  - August 1933: Issue 6 (Box 8, Volume 16)
    Cover by J. W. Schlaikjer -- "Hospital Case" by Roger Torrey and "Dark Death" by Raoul Whitefield
  - September 1933: Issue 7 (Box 8, Volume 16)
    Cover by J. W. Schlaikjer -- "A Woman Can Kill" by Raoul Whitefield and "Whispering Justice: An Ed Jenkins Story" by Erle Stanley Gardner
  - October 1933: Issue 8 (Box 8, Volume 16)
    Missing cover
  - November 1933: Issue 9 (Box 8, Volume 16)
  - December 1933: Issue 10 (Box 8, Volume 16)
    Cover by J. W. Schlaikjer -- "Dead Men's Shoes" by Erle Stanley Gardner
- 1934
  - July 1934: Issue 5 (Box 2, Volume 17)
    Cover by J.W. Schlaikjer -- "If Murder Can Be Funny" by Eugene Cunningham and "Smart Aleck Kill" by Raymond Chandler; Folder 37
  - October 1934: Issue 8 (Box 2, Volume 17)
    Cover by Fred Craft -- "Finger Man" by Raymond Chandler; Folder 38
  - January 1934: Issue 11 (Box 8, Volume 16)
    Cover by J. W. Schlaikjer -- "Private War" by Roger Torrey, "High Murder" by Raoul Whitfield and "A Guest of the House" by Erle Stanley Gardner
  - February 1934: Issue 12 (Box 8, Volume 16)
    very brittle; Cover by J. W. Schlaikjer -- "Ice and Snow" by James Duncan and "Death on Fifth Avenue" by Raoul Whitefield; photocopy of "Clean Sweep" by Roger Torrey (pages 71-86) and "Red Goose" by Norbert Davis (pages 87-99)
  - March 1934: Issue 1 (Box 8, Volume 17)
    Cover by J. W. Schlaikjer -- "Hunch" by Paul Cain and "Cop Killers" by Erle Stanley Gardner
  - April 1934: Issue 2 (Box 9, Volume 17)
    Cover by J. W. Schlaikjer -- "New Twenties" by Erle Stanley Gardner and "Death by Appointment" by Francis Cockrell
  - May 1934: Issue 3 (Box 9, Volume 17)
    Cover by J. W. Schlaikjer -- "Six Have Died" by Carroll John Daly
  - June 1934: Issue 4 (Box 9, Volume 17)
    Cover by A. Redmond -- "Take It and Like It" by Frederick Nebel
  - July 1934: Issue 5 (Box 9, Volume 17)
    Cover by J. W. Schlaikjer -- "Murder Can Be Funny" by Eugene Cunningham
  - August 1934: Issue 6 (Box 9, Volume 17)
    Cover by Fred Craft -- "Murder Book" by Carroll John Daly
  - September 1934: Issue 7 (Box 9, Volume 17)
    very brittle; Cover by Fred Craft -- "The Heavenly Rat" by Erle Stanley Gardner
  - October 1934: Issue 8 (Box 9, Volume 17)
    Cover by Fred Craft -- "Finger Man" by Raymond Chandler; photocopy of "Best Man" by Thomas Walsh (p. 109-123)
  - November 1934: Issue 9 (Box 9, Volume 17)
    Cover by Fred Craft -- "Race Williams Crashes Through" by Carroll John Daly, "Hot Cash" by Erle Stanley Gardner, and " Law and Disorder" by Roger Torrey
  - December 1934: Issue 10 (Box 9, Volume 17)
    Cover by Fred Craft -- "An Old Spanish Custom" by Eugene Cunningham and "Murder isn't Legal" by W. T. Ballard
- 1935
  - January 1935: Issue 11 (Box 2, Volume 17)
    Cover by Fred Craft -- "Killer in the Rain" by Raymond Chandler; Folder 39
  - June 1935: Issue 4 (Box 2, Volume 18)
    Cover by Rudolf Belarski -- "Nevada Gas" by Raymond Chandler; Folder 40
  - November 1935: Issue 9 (Box 2, Volume 18)
    Cover by John Drew -- "Spanish Blood" by Raymond Chandler and "Winter Kill" -- by Frederick Nebel; Folder 41
  - January 1935: Issue 11 (Box 9, Volume 17)
    Cover by Fred Craft -- "Killer in the Rain" by Raymond Chandler
  - February 1935: Issue 12 (Box 9, Volume 17)
    Cover by Fred Craft -- "It's a Gag" by Frederick Nebel and "Casy--Detective" by George Harmon Coxe
  - March 1935: Issue 1 (Box 9, Volume 18)
    Cover by Fred Craft -- "Ghost of a Chance" by Frederick Nebel
  - April 1935: Issue 2 (Box 9, Volume 18)
    Cover by Fred Craft -- "Women are Trouble" by George Harmon Coxe
  - May 1935: Issue 3 (Box 9, Volume 18)
    Cover by Fred Craft -- "A Chance to Cheat" by Erle Stanley Gardner, "That's Kennedy" by Frederick Nebel, and "Win, Place, Show" by Roger Torrey
  - June 1935: Issue 4 (Box 9, Volume 18)
  - July 1935: Issue 5 (Box 9, Volume 18)
    Cover by Rudolph Belarski -- "Murderer's Guest" by Theodore A. Tinsley
  - August 1935: Issue 6 (Box 9, Volume 18)
    Cover by Rudolph Belarski -- "Die-Hard" by Frederick Nebel and "Broadway Babe" by John Lawrence
  - September 1935: Issue 7 (Box 9, Volume 18)
    Cover by Rudolph Belarski -- "Double for Danger" by Sinclair Gluck; pages 98- 108 are missing
  - October 1935: Issue 8 (Box 9, Volume 18)
    Cover by Rudolph Belarski -- "Mr. Casey Flashguns Murder" by George Harmon Coxe and "Crash and Carry" by Erle Stanley Gardner
  - November 1935: Issue 9 (Box 9, Volume 18)
    Cover by John Drew -- "Winter Kill" by Frederick Nebel and "Spanish Blood" by Raymond Chandler
  - December 1935: Issue 10 (Box 10, Volume 18)
    Cover by John Drew -- "Red Death" by Eric Taylor
- 1936
  - January 1936: Issue 11 (Box 2, Volume 18)
    Cover by John Drew -- "Guns at Cyrano's" by Raymond Chandler; Folder 42
  - March 1936: Issue 1 (Box 3, Volume 19)
    Cover by John Drew -- "The Man Who Liked Dogs" by Raymond Chandler; Folder 1
  - June 1936: Issue 4 (Box 3, Volume 19)
    "Goldfish" by Raymond Chandler; Folder 3
  - September 1936: Issue 7 (Box 3, Volume 19)
    Cover by John Drew -- "The Curtain" by Raymond Chandler; Folder 4
  - January 1936: Issue 11 (Box 10, Volume 18)
    Cover by John Drew -- "Guns at Cyrano's" by Raymond Chandler
  - February 1936: Issue 12 (Box 10, Volume 18)
    Cover by John Drew -- "No Hard Feelings" by Frederick Nebel
  - March 1936: Issue 1 (Box 10, Volume 19)
    Cover by John Drew -- ""The Man Who Liked Dogs" by Raymond Chandler; photocopy of "The Man Who Liked Dogs (pp. 10-33); original pages missing (pp. 9- 34).
  - April 1936: Issue 2 (Box 10, Volume 19)
    Cover by John Drew -- "Crack Down" by Frederick Nebel and "Blood on the Moon" by W. T. Ballard
  - May 1936: Issue 3 (Box 10, Volume 19)
    Cover by John Drew -- "Murder Mixup" by George Harmon Coxe; photocopy of "Murder Mixup" (pp. 8-30)
  - June 1936: Issue 4 (Box 10, Volume 19)
    Cover and body are missing--only Contents page remains. There is a copy of this issue in the Raymond Chandler Collection, coll. 638, Box 3. f.3
  - July 1936: Issue 5 (Box 10, Volume 19)
    Cover by John Drew -- "The Calloused Hand" by Eric Taylor and "Nothing Personal" by H. H. Stinson
  - August 1936: Issue 6 (Box 10, Volume 19)
    Cover by John Drew -- "Deep Red" by Frederick Nebel, "Homicide Cue" by Nels Leroy Jorgensen, and "You Can't Bribe Bullets" by John K. Butler
  - September 1936: Issue 7 (Box 10, Volume 19)
    Cover by John Drew -- "The Curtain" by Raymond Chandler
  - October 1936: Issue 8 (Box 10, Volume 19)
    Cover by John Drew -- "Jail Bait" by Roger Torrey and "No Rest for Soldiers" by John K. Butler
  - November 1936: Issue 9 (Box 10, Volume 19)
    Cover by John Drew -- "Double or Nothing" by George Harmon Coxe and "A Guy Has a Thousand Dollars" by H. H. Stinson; Back cover is missing.
  - December 1936: Issue 10 (Box 10, Volume 19)
    Cover by John Drew -- "Angelfish" by Lester Dent
- 1937
  - January 1937: Issue 11 (Box 3, Volume 19)
    Cover by Wilbur Thomas -- "Bulldog" by Max Brand and "Try the Girl" by Raymond Chandler; Folder 5
  - January 1937: Issue 11 (Box 10, Volume 19)
    Cover by Wilbur Thomas -- "Bulldog" by Max Brand
  - February 1937: Issue 12 (Box 10, Volume 19)
    Cover by John Drew -- "Fish to Fry" by Baynard H. Kendrick; Magazine is very brittle.
  - March 1937: Issue 1 (Box 10, Volume 20)
    Cover by Harry Stoner
  - April 1937: Issue 2 (Box 10, Volume 20)
    Cover by Stockton Mulford -- "Manhatten Whirligig" by Theodore Tinsley
  - May 1937: Issue 3 (Box 10, Volume 20)
    Cover by Wilbur Thomas
  - June 1937: Issue 4 (Box 10, Volume 20)
    Cover by J. George Janes; Back cover is missing.
  - July 1937: Issue 5 (Box 10, Volume 20)
    Cover by Wilbur Thomas -- "Flight at Sunrise" by Dwight V. Babcock
  - August 1937: Issue 6 (Box 10, Volume 20)
    Cover by Wilbur Thomas -- "Murder is News" by Theodore Tinsley
  - September 1937: Issue 7 (Box 11, Volume 20)
  - October 1937: Issue 8 (Box 11, Volume 20)
    Cover by Raymond S. Pease
  - November 1937: Issue 9 (Box 11, Volume 20)
    Cover by Stockton Mulford
  - December 1937: Issue 10 (Box 11, Volume 20)
    Cover by J. George Janes -- "Club Fighter" by John Lawrence
- 1938
  - January 1938: Issue 11 (Box 11, Volume 20)
  - February 1938: Issue 12 (Box 11, Volume 20)
  - March 1938: Issue 1 (Box 11, Volume 21)
  - April 1938: Issue 2 (Box 11, Volume 21)
    Cover by James Lunnon
  - May 1938: Issue 3 (Box 11, Volume 21)
  - June 1938: Issue 4 (Box 11, Volume 21)
    Cover by James Lunnon; Back cover is missing.
  - August 1938: Issue 5 (Box 11, Volume 21)
    Cover by Don Creigh; No back cover
  - September 1938: Issue 6 (Box 11, Volume 21)
  - October 1938: Issue 7 (Box 11, Volume 21)
    Cover by J. George Janes
  - November 1938: Issue 8 (Box 11, Volume 21)
  - December 1938: Issue 9 (Box 11, Volume 21)
- 1939
  - January 1939: Issue 10 (Box 11, Volume 21)
  - February 1939: Issue 11 (Box 11, Volume 21)
  - March 1939: Issue 12 (Box 11, Volume 21)
    Cover by Edgar A. Whitney
  - April 1939: Issue 1 (Box 11, Volume 22)
  - May 1939: Issue 2 (Box 11, Volume 22)
  - June 1939: Issue 3 (Box 11, Volume 22)
  - July 1939: Issue 4 (Box 12, Volume 22)
  - August 1939: Issue 5 (Box 12, Volume 22)
  - September 1939: Issue 6 (Box 12, Volume 22)
  - October 1939: Issue 7 (Box 12, Volume 22)
  - November 1939: Issue 8 (Box 12, Volume 22)
  - December 1939: Issue 9 (Box 12, Volume 22)
- 1940
  - January 1940: Issue 10 (Box 12, Volume 22)
  - February 1940: Issue 11 (Box 12, Volume 22)
  - March 1940: Issue 12 (Box 12, Volume 22)
  - April 1940: Issue 1 (Box 12, Volume 23)
  - June 1940: Issue 2 (Box 12, Volume 23)
    Cover by Rafael DeSoto -- "Clamp Down" by H. H. Stinson